

KLAUDIA KANIA

M 07742149994

E kaniaklauudia@gmail.com

www.kaniaklaudia.myportfolio.com www.behance.net/kaniaklaudia

PROFILE

My passion lies within Graphic Design, I have over four years of experience freelancing as a Graphic Designer and also gained some experience volunteering. I have a strong desire and sheer determination to succeed in this industry.

All I need is an opportunity to put my skills to practice and learn much more.

Words business owners, managers, my colleagues and friends would use to describe me are:

Creative, tough cookie through and through, passionate individual and concise, a true leader, strives for excellence, organised, ambitious and totally dedicate.

SKILLS

- Over 6 years of industry experience across all design disciplines
- UI/UX
- Responsive Design
- Design Thinking
- Branding
- Basic HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT
- Client Management
- Taking criticism on my work
- Typography
- Advertising
- Calligraphy
- Photography
- Social Media Marketing & Management
- Retouching and restoring content, images & videos
- Mailchimp

TOOLS

Hardware

- Apple
- PC

Software

- Adobe CC: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Lightroom, XD, After Effect
- Sketch
- Invision

Office Tools

- Google Apps;
- Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook

CMS

WordPress

EMPLOYMENT

CONTRACT CREATIVE POSITIONS

(2013 to Present)

ASHRAF LAW Graphic Designer

Solicitor's office developing designs and logo used for the business card, posters, brochure web-design and banners. Web design website for the company. www.ashraflaw.co.uk

AURA, BLUEMIST

Freelance Graphic Designer & PR

Managing for coffee and bars social media management and marketing. Providing a variety of visual advertisements and graphics for individual clients.

GLOBE MOTOR VEHICLE SPECIALISTS

Freelance Graphic Designer Manchester Garage Branding.

SALUTION MAGAZINE

Freelance Graphic Designer
Branding, print design for local publication.

Editing images.

VISUAL ARCHITECT (Nov 2018 to Jan 2019) Intern Graphic Designer

- Desiging web banners and pannels.
- Creating short animation video in Adobe Effect

LEADX (Dec 2018 - Present) Graphic Designer & Marketing Executive Responsibilities:

- Creating HTML Landing pages
- Manipulating images using Indesign
- Producing marketing collateral e.g. claim packs, letters, forms, emails, sms etc.
- Producing internal marketing materials e.g. scripts, training guides and policy documents.
- Desiging email using Mailchimp.

RAMPANT LION COMPLEX (Feb 2019 - Pres) DIMITRI'S RESTAURANTS (2014 - 2017)

In-House Graphic Designer, Social Media Manager & Marketing Executive Responsibilities:

- Managing all social media posts and restaurant campaigns every month without fail.
- Consistently being one step ahead of my competitors taking eye-catching photographs, editing and retouching, short Instagram videos.
- Independently researching innovative ways to enhance the company's image and brand.
- Design creative emails, web banners and pannels. Produce and maintain an email template framework with the latest HTML standards.
- Email monthly newsletter campaigns across a number of websites and subscribers which I designed according to the target audience. Ongoing reports for all email campaigns and social media.

LTE GROUP, MANCHESTER (Sept 2017)

Volunteer Graphic Designer - Work Placement Responsibilities:

- Working in a pressurised environment closely with the marketing team which consisted of 20 people, included printers, photographers, and illustrators, designers, developers and marketing specialists on multiple briefs and their interpretation of what that they expected.
- Exceeding expectations.
- I would brainstorm ideas, images based on the information, I collated, created a design, presented and discussed the design and changes that may be required and produced a final piece.
- Determining the size and arrangement of illustrative material.
- Developing the overall layout and production design for advertisements, brochures, posters.
- Reviewing final layouts consistently thinking creatively to produce new ideas, concepts and developing an interactive design.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2017

BA (Hons) Creative Media & Visual Communication Manchester Metropolitan University 2014 - 2016

Foundation Degree of Graphic Design & Advertising University of Salford

2012 - 2014 Level 2 & 3, Art & Graphic Design The Manchester College